Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Zoe Davis,January 3, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,January 3, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,January 9, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: P. Dean,January 10, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: The Ruffs,January 11, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Thelma,January 13, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,January 17, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Anna,January 30, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,February 1, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,February 1, 20, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,April 17, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice Blanche Corbett,February 5, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,February 16, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie,February 17, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Uncle Harry, Aunt Zoe, and Wilson Davis,February 22, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie,February 26, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Inez Stone,February 27, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,March 1, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,March 25, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Roberta Sanford,April 11, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Earl Tweedie?,April 14, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,April 20, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,May 1, 11, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Florence and Uncle Nell,May 9, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,May 22, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. W. McLain,June 9, 17, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Clara Miller,June 15, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. W. McLain,June 16, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Tillie,July 17, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy M,July 18, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: D. A. Wright,July 23, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,July 26, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Code Manufacturing Company,July 30, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice,August 2, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia M. Eaton,August 10, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gran Ma,August 10, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. A. Field,August 10, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna,August 16, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,August 17, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. J. Bowker,August 17, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Albion State Bank,August 18, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Mama (NDF),August 27, 31, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. W. McLain,August 30, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ethel,August 31, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Contract with Springport Schools,September 6, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. J. Bowker,September 7, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,September 11, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Carleton,September 13, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,September 18, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Louisa,September 29, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Louisa,October 2, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,October 4, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice Corbett, Anna,October 10, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,October 21, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: International Harvester Company,December 8, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,December 11, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Bertie McMurtrie,December 11, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,December 13-14, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,December 21, 27, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,December 22, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Florence,December 27, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley, Harry C. Finley From: Thelma Beatrice Thompson,December 29, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,January 9, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,January 11, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lena Hewitt,January 12, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dana Richardson,January 23, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,January 24, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,January 27, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Harry and Zoe Davis,February 11, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Wilson Davis,February 11, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,February 16, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Uncle Harry and Aunt Zoe Davis,March 1, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Hazel,March 7, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,March 16, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,March 26, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 154)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,March 29, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt S. Miller,April 2, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary C. Spencer,April 6, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice,April 23, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,May 4, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Pruda,May 4, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: H. J. Lamb,May 10, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Pruda and Philip Hoot,May 16, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice, Anna,June 6, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,June 17, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,June 20, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry Davis,June 22, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bernice,June 14, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,July 15, 19, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama, Papa,July 12, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 169)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama,July 14, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 170)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertrude and Earl Tweedie,July 19, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 171)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,July 31, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 172)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Zoe Davis,August 1, 3, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 173)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie M. Hartung,August 9, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 174)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,August 10, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 175)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama, Papa,August 15, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 176)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Rose McMurtrie,August 18, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 177)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Frances, Kenneth,August 21, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 178)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Nellie (NDF),August 26, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 179)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt S. Miller,September 20, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 180)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,October 15, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 181)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lena,October 22, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 182)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gran Ma Finley,October 26, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 183)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Berien Campbell and Helen Chapel,November 4, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 184)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,November 5, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 185)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Susan Staley Hill,November 6, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 186)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Cousin Anna,November 15, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 187)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Michigan State University Library,November 20, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 188)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,November 23, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 189)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Hobart,November 26, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 190)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: State Library,November 27, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 191)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Albion State Bank,December 9, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,December 11, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lena,December 17, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Fred and Rose McMurtrie,December 18, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 195)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fred and Rose McMurtrie,December 18, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 196)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna,December 19, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 197)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Zoe and Harry Davis,December 20, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Etta Leidy,December 22, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: E. H.,January 3, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mr. and Mrs. L. C. Field,January 4, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Thera,January 21, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Fred and Rose McMurtrie,February 9, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 203)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,February 18, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 204)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,February 25, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 205)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mama (NDF),March 16, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 206)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,March 21, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 207)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,April 13, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 208)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,April 16, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 209)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,May 9, 11, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 210)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry Davis,May 15, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 211)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna and the Corbetts,May 16, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Genevieve,June 6, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 213)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Helen Peckham,June 13, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 214)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Mama,June 18, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 215)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie,August 8, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 216)
  - Correspondence to: W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,August 13, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 217)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ethel,August 15, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,September 9, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Donahue-Adams Company,September 14, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 220)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Carleton,September 24, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 221)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,September 24, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 222)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,October 21, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Helen Clarke,October 25, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 224)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mrs. L. Field,October 26, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 225)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: World Book Company,October 26, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,October 28, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Correspondence to: A. D. White From: NDF,October 30, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,October 31, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 229)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Walter Grant,November 1, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: E. T. Brusie World Book Company,November 12, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,November 18, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 232)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Genevieve,December 8, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,December 11, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: the Stones,December 17, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lena, Frank,December 19, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,December 20, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Arthur Destree,December 26, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley, Harry C. Finley From: Thelma Thompson,December 27, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Pruda,December 28, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 240)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: H. Y. Lamb,December 29, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice,December 31, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 242)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: NDF,[no month] 7, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,[no month, no day] 1924 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Hazel,January 15, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,January 1, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Lena,January 1, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: Miss Nellie McMurtrie From: Bernadine Klohn,January 2, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna,January 3, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Albion State Bank,January 12, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Albion State Bank,January 12, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,January 20, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,December 26, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Albion State Bank,January 29, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Uncle Nell, Aunt Florence,January 31, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Helen Millard, with small Photograph of a Church in Frontier, Michigan,February 3, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: Miss Nellie McMurtrie From: H. L. Routier,February 6, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Anna,February 8, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Alice Grout,February 9, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,February 10, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,February 11, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Rose McMurtrie,February 11, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Uncle Harry, Aunt Zoe, and Wilson Davis,February 23, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,March 9, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis and All From: Harry E. Davis,March 2, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Donahue-Adams Company,March 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Genevieve,March 31, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 7, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Earl,April 15, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Tacoma cousins,April 16, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Treasury Department,May 5, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Helen Clarke,May 9, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: Girl Scouts of Springport From: Helen Clarke,May 9, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Alice,May 12, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Anna,May 14, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Anna,May 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Zoe Davis,June 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,June 30, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Invitation to Senior Banquet,June 4, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertrude,June 25, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Field,June 26, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,June 28, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Mama,July 8, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama,July 25, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Florence,July 3, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Carleton,July 15, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: NDF,July 17, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zoe Davis,July 18, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Earl,August 12, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Earl,August 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 10, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,August 10, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie,August 20, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Wedding Announcement,August 25, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice,August 27, 19uu (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Helen Millard,September 23, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,September 25, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,September 9, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Zoe Davis,September 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ginn and Company,September 23, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie,October 12, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,October 21, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,October 22, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,December 3, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,November 7, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Earl, Gertrude,November 10, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,November 20, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Helen C. Clarke, Brochure on the Sunnycrest School for Girls,December 5, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Dorothy Geiger,December 16, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: the Stone Family,December 19, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: Nellie McMurtrie From: Mrs. Stone,December 20, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Grace Carleton,December 22, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Lena and Uncle John,December 22, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Lida Miller,December 23, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Nelson and Florence Finley,December 28, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,December 31, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Alice,January 11, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Floyd H. Loser,January 9, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Helen Clarke,January 3, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Zarita,January 9, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. J. E. Adams From: Sidney Tench,January 15, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sidney Tench,January 15, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,January 18, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Donahue-Adams Company,January 21, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W. W. McLain,January 29, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Miller,February 6, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Wilson Davis (Nephew),January 13, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. H. W. Sintz From: NDF,February 28, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Universal Institute,February 18, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: George and Ina Stone, with Miscellaneous Newspaper Clipping,March 1, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Harry E. Davis,March 3, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence to: Harry C. Finley From: Mama (NDF),March 11, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Carleton,April 5, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence to: Theron W. Finley From: Uncle Harry and Aunt Zoe Davis,April 9, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Earl,April 12, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: A. J. Skinner,April 13, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence to: Kate Bromeling From: L. C. Monks,April 21, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry,May 6, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Louie,May 11, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice,May 18, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: D. M. McAuliffe,April 13, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Citizens Mutual Auto Insurance Company,October 1, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Gertie,May 5, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace Waterman,May 25, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 102)